收工时间到啦
That's it for tonight.
可以来数小费罐了
Time to count the tip jar.
请为我套上手部避孕套
Hand condom.
我真服了你
I can't believe you.
现在这个年代不流行戴套啦
Using protection is so five years ago.
这里是威廉斯堡
This is Williamsburg.
钞票都很可能染有疱疹
There's a good chance even the dollars have herpes.
如果这些小婊钞票有疱疹
Well, if those singles have herpes,
她们就该跟那些单身婊一样 撒谎装没病
they should just lie about it till they get married
直到骗到婚为止啊
like everybody else does.
太好了 你们还没关门
Oh, good, you're still open.
是的 请问您想要什么
Oh, yes, we are. What can I get you?
收银台里的东西全交出来
Everything in the register.
妈呀 嬉皮士来抢劫了
Oh, my God. It's a hipster hold-up.
快照我说的做 我有枪哦 亲
Hand it over. I have a gun.
我还想死呢 所以你想都别想
Well, I have a death wish so that's not gonna work.
听好了 我们每晚二到四点在这卖小蛋糕
Look, pal, we work at this cupcake window 2:00 to 4:00,
一周卖六天
six nights a week,
而且是在拿着基本工资的隔壁破餐厅
and that is after eight hours of slinging hash
做完八小时的服务员后才来卖的
at the diner next door for lousy minimum wage,
就因为一帮在...
which a bunch of rich politicians out in--
-帮我接 -首都华盛顿
- help me out. - Washington.
有钱的死政客 不愿提高基本工资
What she said-- don't wanna raise.
下班后我们走回我们非法的一卧室公寓中
Then, we walk home to our illegal one bedroom apartment,
靠喝了犯困的感冒糖浆睡三小时
get three hours of Nyquil induced sleep
然后就得起床 两人再一起分享一碗
before we have to get back up and share a bowl
西班牙名的杂牌早餐"卖圈"
of Spanish language cheerios.
跟美国"麦圈"差不多 就字样戴了墨西哥帽
It's the same thing but the "C" wears a sombrero.
所以不行 我才不会给你我们的血汗钱
So, no, I am not about to give you our hard-earned money.
如果你要开枪打我 最好瞄准点
And if you're gonna shoot me, better aim good.
因为如果你没打死我 我会爬过这个收银台
'cause if you miss, I will climb over this counter,
扒开你个死人头 用你的脑袋当新的小费罐
tear off your head, and it'll be our new tip jar.
我刚抢完披萨店
Yeah, I just robbed Pizza Pizza.
这20块你拿去
Here's a $20.
祝你们今晚愉快
Have a good night.
我有特殊的打交道技巧
I have a way with people.
我刚发现我们小蛋糕店的竞争对手
Look, I just saw that our cupcake competition,
"布鲁克林咬一口"关门大吉了呢
"Brooklyn Bitty Bites," went out of business.
没错 现在改成医用大麻店了
Yup, it's being changed into a medical marijuana store.
我已经整了一张积点卡
I already have my hole-punch card.
买四发大麻巧克力蛋糕 第五发免费挑
Buy four brownies and the fifth buzz is free.
"布鲁克林咬一口"咬死了
Brooklyn Bitty Bites bit it!
爽 我们赢了
Yeah! We won!
吃屎去吧 带着亚洲女儿的红发妞
Eat it, red haired lady and your asian daughter!
麦克斯 它们紧接着在小蛋糕界巨擘
Max, them going down right after the death
"小蛋糕屑"后倒闭很可怕好吗
of the cupcake giant, "Crumbs," is scary.
感觉就像外面有个连环杀手
It's like there's a serial killer out there
专门追杀小蛋糕们
coming after cupcakes.
那应该很容易就能逃脱他魔爪啦
Well, he should be easy to outrun,
因为他肯定是个"嗜血肥医"
'cause that'll be one fat Dexter.
说真的 我们有大麻烦了
Seriously, we have a big problem.
我回来啦
I'm back!
我们的"小"麻烦来了
And there's our little problem.
哇 平常很难看到腹语术者的玩偶
Wow, you don't usually see the ventriloquist's dummy
会跑出箱子自己走呢
out of his suitcase alone.
你好 厄尔 你好 卡洛琳
Hello, Earl. Hello, Caroline.
你好 每周三上班前我都得花两小时
Hello, reason I do two hours of phone therapy
看电话心理医生的理由
every Wednesday before work.
所以 你们想我吗
So, did you all miss me?
你之前不在吗
You were gone?
我记得我昨天才见过你啊
'Cause I swear I just saw you yesterday.
不对 我看到的可能是只猫
Wait, maybe that was a cat.
我之前不在好吗
I was gone, people!
我去旧金山参加会议了
To San Francisco for a convention.
潮流饭店与劲爆餐厅协会
The restaurant and diner association.
简称"潮爆"
"Radass."
你去旧金山参加了名为"潮爆"的活动吗
You were at something called "Radass" in San Francisco?
你确定不是"菊爆"吗
Are you sure it wasn't "Redass"?
我又不是基 只是对餐厅性向不定
I am not gay. I'm restaurant curious.
我发现了一个可以加进菜单的新东西
I discovered an exciting new item for our menu.
不行 不许往菜单里加新东西
No way. No new menu additions.
我都已经辗转难眠
I already lie awake in bed
担心咱们店里的食物标准会高到没边了
worrying about how high the food bar is here.
上菜 手撕猪肉
Pick up! Pulled pork.
味道很棒 因为在我手撕[拔出]之前
And it's good 'cause before I pulled it,
我帮他干擦[打飞机]了一遍
I gave it a dry rub.
是4块钱吐司啦
It's $4 toast.
4块钱吐司吗
$4 toast?
比咱们店里吐司的实际身价高了5块钱啊
That's $5 more than our toast is worth.
美味的自制手工面包
Delicious, homemade artisan bread.
一开始 我也不乐意把这么"大"的东西放入嘴
At first, I was reluctant to put something so big in my mouth.
入口后 热腾腾的"黄油"慢慢流下我下巴
But the hot butter drizzling down my chin
简直像是给我"黏糊糊"的赏赐
was my sticky reward.
阿憨 那个吐司是潮流美食
Han, that toast is trendy foodie food.
在这里只会死去 就像我的灵魂
It'll die here, like my soul did.
我们的顾客都只是平凡的普通人罢了
Our customers are just plain, normal people.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
以及苏菲
And sophie.
你们猜怎么着
Guess what?
陌陌上有78个男的想约我
78 guys want me on Tinder.
79个了
Oh, 79!
现在80个了
Now it's 80!
你玩陌陌多久了啊
How long have you been on Tinder?
十分钟
Ten minutes!
看呀 我的老天爷
Oh, look, oh, my gosh!
这男的是猛男水管工 不是骗我吧
This guy's a plumber. Are you kidding me?
当然好 给约
Yes, that's a match!
而这家伙还裸上身呢
And this guy isn't even wearing a shirt!
确定一定以及肯定给约
That's another big yes!
天啊 姑娘们 我会在这里
Oh, gosh, girls, I'll be over here,
在我的卡座里挑男宠
looking at boys in my booth.
我就认识一个女的在陌陌上认识她老公的
Hey, I know a girl who met her husband on tinder.
等等 不 她是在陌陌上抓到她老公
No, wait, she saw her husband on tinder.
坐轮椅的有轮椅诱惑吗
Hey, are wheelchairs sexy?
看看是谁坐在上面吧
I guess it depends on who's in one.
不给约
I say no.
各位观众稍安勿躁
Hold the presses.
我的好姐妹发了条新推特啦
I just got a new tweet from my gal,
金·卡戴珊
Kim Kardashian.
她在曼哈顿买了双新靴子
Oh, she just bought her some new boots in Manhattan.
金·卡戴珊超屌
Kim Kardashian is epic.
她还上了《时尚》杂志的封面 超火
She was on the cover of Vogue. She's on fire.
那又怎样 我也超火过啊
So? I've been on fire.
我上次用巫术来弄免费零食时 被人当女巫烧
That's the last time I try witchcraft for the free snacks.
我好爱卡戴珊家族的人
I love the Kardashians.
她们就像是有大屁股的肯尼迪家族
They're like the Kennedys but with bigger asses.
下次用短信联系我
Text me next time.
讲话这事太傻逼了
This whole talking thing is insane.
你们好
Hi!
如果我想找麦克斯自制小蛋糕店的老板
Who would I talk to about finding the owner
请问我该找哪位呢
of Max's Homemade Cupcakes?
她是麦克斯 我叫卡洛琳
That's Max. I'm Caroline.
我们共同拥有这家店
We're the owners of this store.
我们还拥有大概四双袜子
And about four pairs of socks.
太好了 真棒 这家店超有爱
Great. Wonderful. Such a cute shop.
你们有兴趣参加一档出名的...
Would you be interested in having a popular--
好
Yes.
我都还没说完呢
I didn't finish my sentence.
抱歉 我太久没听到"出名"这个词了
Sorry, I just haven't heard the word "popular" in so long.
是啊 她过气了
Oh, yeah, she's over.
她就像过气倒光的百事达一样
She's the Blockbuster video of people.
那你们有兴趣让
Would you be interested in having
一档出名的真人秀在这里拍摄吗
a popular reality show filmed here?
你...
Y--
抱歉 我得接一下电话
I'm so sorry. I have to take this.
稍等一分钟
Just a minute.
干嘛
What?
有屁快放 说吧
Just say it already. Come on.
麦克斯 这太棒了 想想我们的曝光率
Max, this is great. Think of the exposure.
不知道是哪一档真人秀要拍
I wonder which reality show it is.
会不会是《高中生孕妇》节目
Ooh, maybe 16 and Pregnant is doing
要拍摄"若干年后"特别集 然后找到我啦
a "where are they now" segment and they found me.
或者是跟你有关的"甜心没波来啦"
Or that one about you, "Here comes honey boobless."
你知不知道老娘是谁
Do you have any idea who I am?
要么照做 要么滚蛋
You just do what I say or you are out!
好的
Okay.
妈咪也爱你
Mommy loves you.
抱歉 我宝宝的非籍保姆
Sorry, my baby's Nigerian.
如果要住在这个国家 你得学这里的语言啊
I mean, if you're gonna live here, learn the language.
真是的
Jeez.
所以你们意下如何
So what are we thinking?
超喜欢 我们愿意 是哪一档节目呢
We'd love it. We're in. What show?
《与卡戴珊姐妹同行》
Keeping up with the Kardashians.
终于 老天爷对我们开了门
Finally, God opens a door.
但我要关上窗
And I'm closing a window.
麦克斯
Max!
她有点兴奋过度 超粉你们
She's overwhelmed. Big fan.
能拿一张名片吗
Do you have a card?
记得 短信联系
And listen, text me.
别打给我 我会抓狂
Don't call. It freaks me out.
告诉我为什么
Just give me one good reason
我们不该与卡戴珊姐妹们同行
why we shouldn't keep up with the Kardashians.
我能给你五个好理由
I'll give you five good reasons.
金 金波 金朗代克
Kim, Kamber, Klondike...
还有两个小的 金脆皮与金奶油
and the little ones, Krispy and Kreme.
听你胡扯
Not even close.
行 金 金怪 金爱[酷爱牌饮料]
Fine. Kim, Kooky, Kool-aid,
还有年纪小点的 金袋鼠与金队长
and the little ones, Kaptain and kangaroo.
是金 考特妮 科勒 凯莉与肯达尔
It's Kim, Kourtney, Khloe, Kylie, and Kendall.
她妈妈真带种 给她取那名
That mother has some nerve, naming a kid
她估计都没读过"Kindle"这本书吧
who's probably never even read a book "Kindle."
我们非上不可
We need this.
大家都在看这档节目
Everyone watches Keeping up with the Kardashians.
感觉就像《与星共舞》
It's like Dancing with the Stars,
但是没有明星
but without the stars.
所以跟《与星共舞》一模一样
So, Dancing with the Stars.
那你得告诉我这节目我会讨厌的一个点
Okay, tell me one good thing about this show that I hate,
因为我从来没看过
'cause I've never seen it.
这节目是在说这个家族
Well, it's all about this family
以及他们的挣扎 只为...
and their struggle to...
跟别人同行
keep up.
好吧 我也从来没看过
Yeah, okay. I've never seen it either.
苏菲 谢谢你同意让我们下班后
Sophie, thank you so much for letting us come up
来你这里看电视
after work to watch your tv.
麦克斯把我们的旧电视变成了大麻烟斗
Max turned our old one into a bong.
那次我也被人当女巫烧了
That was another time I was on fire.
你们想看哪一集
Well, which episode do you want to watch?
"金买了新帽子"
"Kim gets a new hat."
还是"凯利在音乐节大哭"
or "Kylie cries at Coachella"?
还是"科勒剃阴毛"
Or "Khloe gets a bikini wax"?
这集超经典
Now that one's a classic.
你录了多少集啊
How many of these do you have DVR'd?
这台电视存了17集
Well, I got 17 on this tv
卧室里那台存了53集
and 53 on the one in the bedroom.
我喜欢听着金的声音入睡
I like to go to sleep with the sound of Kim's voice.
听她说招牌金句入眠
It's so comforting when she says,
"这真是尴尬到爆"
"this is super awkward."
而且有时候她还会拱起背
And you know, sometimes she arches her back
然后说那句话 像这样
when she says it, like this.
"这真是尴尬到爆"
"This is super awkward."
这真是尴尬到爆
This is super awkward.
如果我当年没离开波兰
You know, I bet you if I stayed in Poland,
我跟我姐我妹们估计也能有一档节目
my sisters and I would have had our own show.
节目名会是《与科臣斯基姐妹同行》
It would've been called, Keeping up with the Kachinskis.
只可惜她们都没活超过20岁
It's too bad we all didn't live to see 20.
太吓人了
It's not cute.
我想要能逗我开心的人
You know I need someone to make me laugh.
金呢 她总是迟到
Where's kim? Kim is always late.
停
Stop!
够了
Enough!
我们到此为止吧
That's it, we're done.
喂 滚出去 都早上了
Hey, get the hell out! It's morning!
我知道 我知道 但我们忍不住
I know, I know, but we couldn't stop
要看她们屁事不做
watching them do nothing.
这节目太他妈天才了
This show is freaking genius!
金发妹是在哭吗
Is the blonde one crying?
克丽丝与金在维也纳的时候
Mm-hmm. Kris and Kim are in Vienna
有人偷走了她的名牌宝缇嘉包包
and someone stole Kris's Bottega bag
以及她在巴黎买的
and her Chanel clutch with the matching pumps
配套香奈儿手包与高跟鞋
that she bought in Paris.
好了 我得先去撒泡晨尿
All right, well, I have to go take my morning tinkle.
等我撒完 我希望你们能离开我家
But when I come back, I want you two to be out of here
我需要用那个秋千来晨练
because I need that swing for my exercises.
我们得上这节目
We have to do this show.
肯定对我们生意大有帮助
It'll be so great for our business.
曝光率唯一有可能比这个高的方法
The only way we'd get more exposure
是奥兰多·布鲁姆与比伯在我们店门口
is if Orlando Bloom and Bieber bitchslapped each other
像娘们一样呼扇巴掌
in front of our shop.
谁管我们的生意怎么样啊
Who cares about our business?
我超想被她们妈妈领养
I want that mother to adopt me!
她的小孩流出性爱视频 她借机捞了几百万
Her kid makes a sex tape, she turns it into millions.
而我妈妈对我的性爱视频唯一做过的事
The only thing my mother ever did with my sex tape
就是复制一份给她的男人欣赏
was copy it and give it to her boyfriend.
我好激动呀
I'm so excited.
麦克斯 快看 这是我开心的表情
Max, this is what I look like when I'm happy.
你以前从未有幸见过哦
You've never seen it.
请叫我的新名字
Please call me by my new name,
金原体·卡戴珊
Khlamydia Kardashian.
不许再说这么白痴的话
Don't say anything stupid like that.
我一句话都不用说
I won't have to say anything.
克丽丝只要看我一眼 就能认出我是她的孩子
Kris will see me and recognize me as one of her own
会被我的丰唇 我的巨乳
with my lips, my boobs,
还有我想住进洛杉矶豪宅的决心所打动
and my willingness to live in some place called calabasas.
她们来了 我的人生将从此改变
They're here. My life changes now!
快看 这是我开心的表情
This is what I look like happy.
你以前从未有幸见过哦
You've never seen it.
你好 我们现在超级激动
Hi, we are so, so excited about this.
计划有变
There has been a change.
她们不来了
They're not coming.
穿高跟鞋不好走这么远的道
It's too far to walk in heels.
瞧 她很有可能是我的亲妈
See? She might as well have been my real mom
因为她爱高跟鞋多过爱我
'cause she just chose a heel over me.
你们好啊 我来见我的闺蜜小金金啦
Hi, here I am to meet Kiki, my bff.
快看我的新裙子 跟小金金是姐妹裙哦
And look at my new dress! Twinsies!
好一对"大"姐妹啊
They certainly are.
抱歉 她不来了
Sorry, she's not coming.
节目改到坚宝果汁店拍摄了
We had to film them in jamba juice instead.
这真是尴尬到爆
Well, this is super awkward.
卡戴珊一家全是白痴
Stupid Kardashians!
金 金胖脚踝 金坏脾气
Kim, Kankels, Krank,
还有那两个小的 金缩阴术和金踢蛋蛋
and the little ones, kegel and kickball,
快来亲老娘的金屁股吧
You can kiss my keister.
麦克斯 别闹了 我想睡觉呢
Max, stop it! I'm trying to sleep.
抱歉 但我很生气 现在都早上11点半了
Well, sorry, but I'm pissed and it's 11:30 anyway.
你还躺在床上干嘛呢
What's going on?
即使金·卡戴珊只发一条推特
Even one tweet from Kim would have exposed us
也会有2200万名粉丝知道我们
to 22 million followers.
就连科学神教都没这么多脑残粉呢
Scientology doesn't even have those numbers.
-咱们成不了名都怪她们 -我知道
- They screwed us. - I know.
所以我今天为卡戴珊家族
That is why I'm making hate cupcakes
做了仇恨小蛋糕 瞧
for the Kardashians, see?
"吃屎吧" "咬我啊"
"Eat it," "Bite me,"
还有组合装哦 "找" "份" "工"
And these three... "Get" "A" "Job."
还为妈妈特意准备了一个 "我还爱你哦"
Oh, and one for the mom that says, "I still love you,"
以防万一嘛
Just in case.
快给我起床
Now come on, get up.
你儿子要出去拉一坨8英尺长的屎
Your son needs to go out and take an 8-foot crap.
不要 我受够了
No, I'm done.
如果说人人都不喜欢小蛋糕了 那我也是
If everyone's done with cupcakes, so am I.
我受够了假装一切都会如愿以偿
I'm done pretending that everything's gonna work out.
在我们这出真人秀里 事与愿违
In our reality show, it's not.
快起床 不然我就把你跟床一起合上
Look, get up, or I will close this bed with you in it,
你的新真人秀就是你的真实生活
and your new reality show will be true life:
《夹缝求生》
I live in a wall.
我不要起床 打死都不起
I'm not getting up. Ever.
麦克斯 住手 求你了
Max, stop, stop it! Stop it!
把我放下来 快放我下来
Put me down! Put me down!
怎么了
What's happening?
我的头抬不起来了
I can't lift my head.
我是不是中风了
Did I have a stroke?
冷静 你床上这张床上没男人"马上疯"
Calm down. No one has stroked in your bed
都多久了 有一年了吧
since--what is it, going on a year?
麦克斯 我的头发卡住了
Max. My hair is caught.
我的头发卡住了 我的头发卡住了
My hair is caught! My hair is caught!
你在对谁大吼大叫呢
Who are you yelling at?
整个状况 快帮忙啊
The whole situation! Do something!
我看看
Let me look.
没错 头发全都被床的齿轮卡住了
Oh yeah, it's all caught up in the bed gears here.
天啊 我的床居然有齿轮
Oh my God, I have a bed with gears
现在还把我的头发卡住了
and my hair is caught in it!
不行
Ooh, nope.
被卡得死死的
It's really all stuck up in there.
真是奇了怪了
It's so odd.
怎么会发生这种事呢
I don't know how a thing like this could happen.
因为你想把我关进墙里
Uh, you put me up into the wall.
现在我像穷鬼版长发公主
And now I'm trapped in a murphy bed
被困在一张折叠床上
like some welfare Rapunzel.
别恐慌了 我去拿剪刀
Stop panicking, I'll get a scissors.
是呀是呀 快拿剪刀
Oh, yeah, yeah! Get the scissors.
拿来直接插进我心脏吧
Then plunge 'em into my heart
我宁愿失去生命 也不愿失去秀发
'cause I'd rather die than cut my hair.
好啦 麦克斯 我可能有办法
Okay, Max, I think I have something that might work,
但你得先向我保证
But you have to promise me
你永远都不会再提起这件事
that you will never bring this up again.
哪件事 你的头卡在你的床上吗
What? The fact that your head is stuck to your bed?
抱歉 一不小心又脱口而出了
Sorry, that's coming up again.
打开我的床头柜
Go into my nightstand
拿出我肉桂味的卸妆油
and get my cinnamon-flavored make-up remover.
你是说性爱润滑油吗
You mean the lube?
能不能就把它称为"卸妆油"啊
Can we please call it make-up remover?
求你了 我们俩得口径一致
Please! I need us to do that.
都快用完了
It's almost empty.
老天 你"泄"了不少妆啊
Man, you've removed a lot of make-up.
别晃了 快挤一点出来
Stop it! Just squeeze some out
涂到我们需要移动的部位
and put it on the parts that we need to move.
不用你教 我可是老手了
Yeah, I'm familiar.
拜托告诉我起作用了
Please tell me it's working.
我在试 但是...
I'm trying, but...
我觉得你的头发弄不出来了
I don't think I can get your hair out.
好消息是 里面可以塞个鸡鸡哦
Good news is, I think we can fit a penis in there.
会是谁呢
Who could that be?
一位我们帮他做足前戏的强奸犯
A rapist we've done most of the work for.
我们正说到你呢
Oh, we were just talking about you.
麦克西 你得帮我做阿憨吐司的面包
Max, you gotta help me with the bread for Han's toast.
我已经烤坏了十个这玩意了
I've already burned ten of these.
事实证明 我唯一擅长烤[做]的是冰毒
Turns out the only thing I can successfully bake is meth.
奥列格 快来床上 我需要你
Oleg, come to the bed. I need you!
没问题
All right!
虽然才花了四年时间 但我来了 宝贝
Only took you four years, but I'm here, baby.
不 不是你想的那样 奥列格
No, it's not like that, Oleg.
快过来
Just get over here!
好
Okay.
拿着
Hold this.
厄尔 你怎么会在这
Earl, what are you doing here?
奥列格打给我 说卡洛琳一直大叫
Oleg called me when he couldn't get Caroline
按都按不住
to stop the screaming.
麦克斯 厄尔给我吃了点巧克力蛋糕
Hi, Max. Earl gave me part of a brownie.
事实证明 青光眼和头发被卡住
Turns out, glaucoma and having hair stuck
都可以用同一处方解决
take the exact same prescription.
各位请看
Look!
没错 各位小婊砸
That's right, you mothers!
老子成功了
I did it!
我做出了完美的面包
I made the perfect bread!
你可是一个大厨 居然花了19小时做一个面包
You're a chef who took 19 hours to make one loaf of bread.
史蒂芬·霍金跑百米冲刺都比你行
Stephen Hawking was more successful at the 100-yard dash.
还有你 你明知道
And you-- you are aware
我一路杀进曼哈顿
that I went all the way into Manhattan,
拿小蛋糕轰炸金·卡戴珊住的酒店
cupcake-bombed Kim Kardashian's hotel,
而你还赖在床上不愿起来是吗
and you're still just laying here, right?
难道你都不用尿尿吗
Didn't you have to pee?
我忍住了大部分
I held most of it in.
这太荒谬了 你在床上都躺一天了
This is crazy. You've been here all day.
赶紧把你该死的头发剪了吧
Let's just cut your damn hair already.
如果没有这头秀发 我就不是我了
I wouldn't be me without my hair.
没有它 我将活不下去
I can't live without it.
你可以的
Yes, you can.
没有钱 你活下来了
You have lived without money,
没有电 你活下来了
You've lived without electricity,
没有冲水马桶 你也活下来了
You've lived without plumbing.
那你觉得是什么支撑我度过这些呢
What do you think got me through it?
我的秀发啊
My hair.
我会安慰自己"家财散尽 厕所堵塞
I'd be like, "Lost all my money, the toilet's clogged,
仍有秀发 宽慰我心"
still got my hair."
亲爱的 我觉得巧克力蛋糕没起到作用
Darling, I don't think those brownies are kicking in.
我这还有秘制的棒棒糖哦
I also have some lollipops.
希望你会开心
I hope you're happy.
我从猫眼看不到任何东西
I didn't see anything through the peep-hole,
所以我猜应该是阿憨来了
So I'm guessing it's Han.
各位好啊
Ah, hello!
我的餐厅开门了 却没有员工上班
I have an open diner and no diner staff!
阿憨 快看 我做出了完美的面包
Han, look, I made perfect bread.
比我之前吃的那种还"大"
It's bigger than I'm used to.
给我一分钟 做个深呼吸
Let me just take a minute and breathe.
我相信我一定能全部"塞进去"
And I'm sure I can take it all in.
如果你需要帮忙
Well, if you need any help,
卡洛琳还剩点"卸妆油"哦
Caroline's got some make-up remover.
小金金发推特了 小金金发推特了
Kiki tweet, Kiki tweet, Kiki tweet!
她说"金·卡戴珊发推特了"
She's saying "Kiki tweet"!
他怎么听懂了 难道他是半人半海豚吗
How did he understand that? Is he part dolphin?
金·卡戴珊拍了一张我的仇恨小蛋糕发上推特
Kim Kardashian tweeted a pic of my mean cupcakes
还写道"麦克斯自制小蛋糕 标签是太过分了"
and said, "Max's Homemade Cupcakes #notcool."
我的老天 我居然认识金·卡戴珊讨厌的人耶
Oh, my God, Kim Kardashian hates someone I know!
有2200万人会看到这条推特
That went out to 22 million people!
-对不起嘛 -干嘛道歉
- I'm so sorry. - Why?
你知道有多少人受不了卡戴珊家族吗
Do you know how many people can't stand the Kardashians?
我们的小蛋糕窗口肯定会爆满
Our cupcake window will be packed!
快帮我剪断
Cut me loose.
卡洛琳 我们俩终于要剪刀[女同做爱]了
Hey, Caroline, we're finally about to scissor.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
我们还有生意要忙
We got a business to run.
快剪吧 我会没事的
Cut it, I'll be fine.
没错 你需要这根棒棒糖
Yeah, you're gonna need that lollipop.
我知道 卡戴珊一家烂透了
Yeah, I know, those Kardashians are the worst.
所以我才没有继续与她们同行
That's why I don't keep up with them anymore.
行了 麦克斯 准备打烊啦
All right, Max. Okay, that's it.
还剩一个 业绩不错
Just one left. Not bad.
你的头发也不错
And your hair's not bad either.
现在才不错
Yeah, now,
多亏了我跑去发廊紧急补救
after the emergency trip to that salon.
你刚剪完我头发时
When you got done with me,
我就像一只在化疗的小鸟
I looked like a baby bird on chemo.
抱歉不得不用掉了我们最后一点存款去剪头发
I'm sorry I had to use the last of our savings for my hair cut.
-你才不抱歉 -当然 我超爱这发型
- No, you're not. - No, I am not, I love this.
你们好 我是金·卡戴珊
Hi, I'm Kim.
我想为之前
I just wanted to say sorry
没能在贵店拍摄节目而道歉
that we didn't film here the other day.
光看她就觉得杀伤力好大啊
It almost hurts to look at her.
我知道我们女生为了自己的事业
I know how hard us girls really work
会有多辛苦
to keep our businesses going,
所以我来买一个小蛋糕
So I'll take a cupcake
然后我真的会帮你们发推宣传
and I'll totally tweet about it for real.
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
给 快拿着
Here, here, here, here, here.
我们找不开100块 不过没关系
We can't break a $100, and anyway,
这个我们请你吃吧
this is so on the house.
谢谢
Oh, thanks.
头发不错
Cute hair.
等等 问你个问题
Wait. Real quick...
你觉得你妈会收养我吗
Do you think your mother would adopt me?
这真是尴尬到爆了
This is super awkward.